# **ART FRICK**

Designer - Developer - Online Accessibility Specialist (646) 400-8927 • artfrick@gmail.com

## **PROFILE**

Creative individual with a background in technology, accessible design, and systems development, with excellent communication and presentation skills, considerable experience in dealing with diverse groups of people, classroom teaching experience, public speaking experience, and a solid work ethic.

## **CORE SKILLS**

Proactive • Goal-oriented • Positive attitude • Natural leader • Team player

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### 2012-Present | University of New Hampshire - Institute on Disability | Westchester, NY

Mission: The Institute on Disability at the University of New Hampshire focuses on the improvement of knowledge, policies, and practices related to the lives of persons with disabilities and their families.

Web Designer - Information Technologist II

- Design and develop accessible solutions for all web-based needs of the organization
- Upgrade and revamp websites for increased usability and performance
- Formulate plans for web-based dissemination of information per grant requirements
- Provide user and systems-level technical support and development for the organization
- Manage external vendor/project relations

#### 2008-2012 | Freelance Designer/Developer | New York, NY

Mission: Provided marketing, web and graphic design, and development services to a diverse client base.

#### Designer/Developer

- Created user interfaces and web assets, including banners ads, Flash animations, and photography
- Developed timelines and maintained client expectations
- Managed freelance and full-time staff members

#### 2006-2008 | Starlite Media, LLC | New York, NY

Mission: Starlite Media is a full service, place-based outdoor advertising company

Vice President of Marketing and Creative Services

- Oversaw all marketing endeavors, including industry event planning, online marketing, and publicity
- Attended industry events to promote products and gain exposure among senior-level media buyers
- Conceptualized, designed, and coordinated production of all sales materials
- Managed department staff and developed internship program

## **EDUCATION**

### 2014-2017(est) | University of New Hampshire | Durham, NH

- M.B.A. Candidate
- 4.0 GPA

#### 2002-2006 | Parsons School of Design | New York, NY

- B.F.A.. Fine Arts
- Graduated with a 3.61 GPA

#### 2000-2002 | Columbia State Community College | Columbia, TN

- A.S., General Transfer
- Graduated with a 3.70 GPA

# **TECHNICAL & RELEVANT SKILLS**

- Adobe CC Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign
- HTML/CSS/JS/PHP/ASP.NET
- WordPress, Drupal, Sitefinity, and Kentico CMS experience
- Version Control (GIT)
- Relational databases (MySQL, MS Access)
- ARIA-spec and WCAG 2.0 standard compliance auditing
- Microsoft Office
- Windows Server administration, setup, and development
- Microsoft Active Directory experience
- Remote systems support
- Classroom and professional-setting teaching experience
- Able to interact and work with large groups of people
- Managerial experience
- Excellent presentation skills
- Able to translate ideas into reality